Jessica Rowntree

123 Main Street, San Diego, CA 12345 j.rowntree@youremail.com (123) 456*7890

Reliable Certified Nursing Assistant with over 11 years of experience in a diverse range of healthcare settings.

Excellent track record of delivering high-quality and compassionate care to aging adults. Friendly disposition and fluent in English and Spanish.

Education

High School Diploma

Bay High School, San Diego,CA,
September 2005 - June 2009

Key Skills

- Patient support
- Excellent communication
- Medication administration
- Vital signs monitoring

Certifications

◆ Certified Nursing Assistant State
 □f California 2009

Professional Experience

Certified Nursing Assistant

Oak Tree Acres Retirement Village, San Diego, CA | December 2016 - Present

- Assist 20+ residents with the activities of daily Living and escorted them to meals and activities
- Provide social and physical support to residents
- Play cognitive games with seniors with memory impairment disorders
- Establish a rapport with seniors to ensure they receive the best care for their individual needs
- Support residents on weekly field trips
- Assist the activity director in coming up with appropriate daily activities for the residents and encourage the residents to take part in activities
- Introduced a new medicine scheduling system that reduced errors by 27%

Certified Nursing Assistant

New Ages Hospital, San Diego, CA | July 2009 - November 2016

- Cared for up to 15 patients in the surgical ward each day
- Observed physical changes in the patients' condition and reported findings to nurses and surgeons
- Assisted patients in transferring from their bed to chair, always ensuring patient safety and comfort
- Followed instructions from senior medical staff regarding patient care